(Sheldon:)I'll be right across the hall.
(Sheldon:)You'll probably be able
to hear it.
(Leonard:)Keep the clock, Sheldon.
(Howard:)Thank you.
Thank you?
(Sheldon:)Oh, now...
(Sheldon:)what about
(Sheldon:)our 3-D chess set?
(Leonard:)Let me guess, you want it.
(Sheldon:)Well, no,
(Sheldon:)I just didn't think you'd want
a physical reminder
(Sheldon:)of a game you never
managed to win.
(Sheldon:)As a kindness, I should probably
take all the games.
(Leonard:)You know what, Sheldon, take it.
(Leonard:)In fact, you can
have everything.
(Leonard:)I really don't care.
(Sheldon:)Are you sure?
(Sheldon:)These items represent
our shared times together.
(Leonard:)Well, now they're yours.
Leonard....
(Leonard:)Well, you know
what's gonna happen.
(Leonard:)He's just gonna come up
with some reason
(Leonard:)why everything should be his.
(Sheldon:)For a man so good
at predicting my moves,
(Sheldon:)how come you stink at 3-D chess?
Sheldon, you're-you're being
a little selfish.
(Amy:)Why don't you let Leonard
keep a few things?
(Sheldon:)It's not my fault
I'm bad at sharing;
(Sheldon:)I skipped kindergarten.
(Leonard:)You know what?
(Leonard:)There is one thing I would like.